In this video, I'm going to show you how
I use AI to create full e-commerce video
ads that look a little something like
this.
>> This new blender is so powerful, it just
might explode. Meet the Jet Smooth
portable blender. It crushes frozen
fruit, ice, and nuts in seconds without
any cords.
>> So, every single visual and every scene
that you're seeing here is completely
made with AI, and nothing is real. I
didn't use my camera or hire anyone to
film all of these shots. This was all
made with a few prompts on Chat GBT and
a little bit of creativity. And in this
video, I'm going to walk you guys step
by step on my process on making all of
this happen with AI, even if you have
zero experience. So, let's get straight
into it.
So, before we get into everything, let
me quickly explain the power of AI and
what other stores are currently doing,
just so you can get an idea of the
potential and how you could be using
this for your store right now. So, I've
showed this store in one of my previous
videos before, but this store called
Maya Apparel is actually one of the
first stores that I seen actually
creating fully AI generated videos that
look like this. And every single scene
that you're seeing here is completely
fake. Like, literally nothing here is
real. And this is what really piqued my
interest. It made me start to learn more
about AI and how to actually generate
moving visuals like this for my own
products. And since using AI ads for my
store, I've been noticing much better
results. You can see at the start of
this month, I did around 6.6K in sales.
And to give a closer look, my total net
profit was actually 1.9K, giving me a
net profit of almost 30%. And if I
scroll down below, we can get a further
breakdown on how I actually made those
profits. So, you can see I spent around
2.3K to fulfill all of my orders, around
$2,000 in total ad spend, and then
around $200 in Shopify transaction fees,
and then, of course, I have other
expenses like paying my VAS and whatnot.
But this is just a general gist of how
much I'm making excluding those factors.
And by the way, if you want to be able
to track your profits really seamlessly,
this app that I'm using is called True
Profit, which I use for all of my
stores. And if you're running a lot of
ads in different platforms, you actually
have the ability to integrate almost
every single ad platform out there, such
as Facebook ads, Google Ads, Tik Tok
ads, and pretty much the list goes on.
And it'll also sync every single product
in your store. And all you have to do is
just set up how much it actually costs
you to fulfill those orders. And once
you set that up, it's going to
automatically calculate your profits in
real time, so you don't have to. So, if
you want to make your life super easy
and know exactly how much your store is
making on a daily basis, then I'd
strongly recommend checking out True
Profit. I'll leave a link down below in
case you want to try it out. All right,
so now let me get into the full process
on how I generated this full video ad
with AI. So, there's going to be a few
foundational things that we're going to
need to do first in order to create a
fully animated video like this. The
first thing that we need is a script
that we can use for our video because
this is really important so we
understand which type of scenes and
visuals we can actually place into the
video that is going to match with the
script. And I'm going to show you how
you can easily make a script for
yourself by using my custom GPT. I'll
link it down below in case you guys want
to use it. But basically, all you need
to do is find another winning video ad,
whether it's on your Facebook feed or
your Tik Tok feed. In this case, I ran
into this video that had 7 million
views. And this is telling me that the
script that they're using is obviously
something that works. And then I simply
copied the URL of that video. I went
over to fdown.net. And then I pasted in
that URL to download the video. Then I
took it over to reream.io io to be able
to transcribe that entire video and give
me the entire script into text form
which I could then simply copy and then
plug it directly into my GPT which is
going to help me create a script for my
own product modeled after the same tone
and the talking style from the script
that I'm giving them. So I quickly just
wrote out this prompt where I just said
help me clone the script for my portable
blender adapt and shorten the script
suited for a 30-se secondond video ad.
And then I'm going to take the full
script that I downloaded and then I'm
going to paste it down below this
prompt. And then I'm also going to drag
over a few images of my product because
this is going to give some more context
on how my product works. And I simply
downloaded all of these files from this
AliExpress listing for this product.
Then after I submitted everything, it
was able to give me this script right
here. However, I didn't really like the
hook that it gave me. So then I just
said to give me five better hooks than
that, and I ended up liking this hook
right here. So then I replied saying to
use this hook and develop a script
around that hook. And then it gave me
this full script right here. And then I
replied to it saying, "Remove the scene
suggestions and give me the script
itself." This way it looks really clean
and easy to read. And then I simply just
copy the script and then paste my script
over to this website called 11 Labs
using their texttospech feature. And
this is basically going to help us
create really realistic sounding voices
that is going to explain our script. So
on the right hand side we have access to
a ton of different realistic voices. In
this case I use this voice called
Vanessa which I thought sounded really
good. And then once I selected my voice
I just clicked on generate speech. And
then once I was happy with my results I
simply downloaded the audio file. And
then I uploaded that script directly
into Cap Cut. And that is exactly how I
was ready to start building the scenes
to match that script. So now the
question is, how do we actually create
all the content that's going to pair
well with the script? So the first thing
that we need to do is generate images
that is going to match every single
scene in our video. So there's a couple
of ways that we can do this. The first
way could be your own creativity and
just simply generating some images from
scratch that you feel like is going to
match specific parts of your script.
Now, if you don't have too much
creativity and you're not too
experienced with using AI, don't worry
because I also have a custom GPT that's
going to help you create image prompts
and video prompts that's going to help
you with the entire process. Let me show
you how this is going to work. So, what
I'm going to do is just drag over some
images of my products so we can give
some context on how my product works.
And then I'm just going to type in a
prompt similar to this where I'm just
basically saying, "Help me make a 30-se
secondond video ad based on this
portable blender." And then I'm also
saying to choose the target demographic
for me, just in case I have zero clue on
what kind of marketing angle I want to
take for this product. And after
submitting that info, it gives me a full
breakdown on the target demographic that
it chose for me. But then it also asks
me a couple of questions. The first one
asks if I have a script that's already
ready to go. This way, it knows exactly
what kind of scenes and images it can
actually generate based on that script.
And then it's also asking how long my
video should be, but I already told them
30 seconds, so I don't know why it's
asking me that. Again, this GBT isn't
perfect, by the way. But this is
basically how I replied. I just said to
develop the scenes around this script
and then I simply took that exact script
that we used to generate with 11 Labs
earlier. So what happens from here is
that it's going to analyze the full
script. It's going to break it down by
the hook, the product intro, features
and benefits and blah blah blah. And
then it's just going to estimate the
video length and how many shots it
thinks it's going to take to be able to
match every single scene for our script.
And you could just have a quick read
over it and see if you like it. And at
the very end, it's going to ask you
whether you're satisfied with that shot
list and whether you want to reduce it
or add more scenes. And if everything
looks good to you, you can just simply
tell them go. And then from here, it
just created a batch of five image
prompts that's going to help us bring
all of those scenes into life. So, what
I'm going to do is copy the very first
prompt. Then I'm going to open a brand
new window of chatbt. Make sure we're on
the 40 model. Then I'm going to paste in
that prompt. And then I'm also going to
drag over a very clear image of the
product that I'm selling, which in this
case is a portable blender. And then I'm
going to press enter and see what kind
of image it's able to create for us. And
here's the result it was able to give
me, which looks like the portable
blender is about to explode, which is
the exact hook shot that you guys saw in
the beginning of this video. And once we
generate our first photo, we just go
back into our GPT, and it's pretty much
a rinse and repeat process. We're going
to copy the prompt for image number two.
We're going to go back into the chat
room, plug in the photo of our product
and also our prompt. And then we're
going to end up with another image that
we could use for our video. So, I
basically just continued to do this, but
this time I copied the exact image that
I generated based on scene two to use it
for context. And then I just copied
prompt number three and then I put it
right here. And then this is the image
it was able to create which I also think
looks pretty good. But now I'm going to
show you some of the problems that you
might face as you continue to generate
more images in the same chat room. So
you can see down below here I uploaded
the same image from scene number two and
then I copied the prompt from image
number four. And if we take a look at
the results here, you can see how it
created this image using the context
from what it created earlier which is
kind of like that same overhead style
shot. So, the reason I'm showing this to
you guys is that when you are generating
multiple images inside of the same chat
room, there can be times where you can
get results that you don't really want
because it's going to pull some context
from some of those previous images. Now,
this is partly due to the fact that at
the very end of our image prompts, it's
always going to have an ending statement
that says to keep the lighting
consistent with prior shots. Now, if you
want to be able to generate some of
these images from scratch without
necessarily pulling some context from
the prior image, then what you can do is
just open up a brand new chat room,
upload a photo of your product, upload
that same prompt, but just delete that
ending statement that says to maintain
the same lighting as previous shots
because obviously there is no previous
shots that this chat room can work with.
And as you can see, it created a brand
new visual from scratch that I
personally think is a whole lot better
than what it created for me here. And
this is what I ended up doing with a lot
of other scenes for my video. Every time
I copied the prompt directly from my
GPT, I would just open up a new chat
room so that I can get some fresh
results. As you can see here, I have all
these separate chat rooms that got me
all of these different images. And one
quick tip I want to give you to make
your image generation much faster and
also have more consistency with your
products. You can also use Sora, which
is directly available in chat GPT. And
inside Sora, we have the ability to
generate images exactly like we could do
in the chat GPT chat rooms. The only
difference is is that we can actually
choose what aspect ratio that we want,
but we can also choose how many
variations we want for every single
submission. So, you can see that I was
able to create a ton of different
visuals that I could use for my video
much faster. And because I could get
four generations every single time, it
was much easier to get the result that I
was looking for. And another thing I
want to mention, if you want to get more
accurate results for your product, I
would recommend to always upload a
clearer photo of your product, but also
include a couple of images that look
more clear, like this on a white
background, as well as specific
close-ups of certain areas of your
product that have really unique designs
or shapes to it. And I found that by
including all of these different visuals
helped to create an image that looked as
close as possible to the product that I
was selling. And once you have a solid
foundation of all of your images, now
I'm going to show you how we can take
all of those images and turn them into
animated videos. just like this so that
we can create one full video ad purely
with AI. But before we get into all of
that, I just wanted to quickly mention
that if you're just a beginner who's
just starting out with e-commerce or
drop shipping and you're looking for a
good solution to source any product that
you want to sell, one quick tip I want
to give you is that you shouldn't be
drop shipping from AliExpress because
number one, it's very hard for you to
know which seller is actually sourcing a
good quality version of your product.
And number two, the customer service
that you're going to get from
AliExpress, especially if you need help
with some of your products that might
arrive damaged to your customers, is not
usually the best in my experience. And
if I was just starting and I want to
source my products with the least
headaches possible, then I would simply
just copy the URL of the product on
AliExpress, take it over to Zenrop, use
their request a product feature and plug
in my URL. This way, they can source the
best quality version of my product, and
also give me really good customer
support in the event I have an issue
with the products that arrive to my
customers. And to make things even
easier, it connects directly to your
Shopify store and syncs all of your
orders in real time. And all you have to
do is select all of your orders at once,
pay for everything in just one click,
and all of your customers are going to
get their tracking numbers
automatically, and it's pretty much
hands-off from there. I'll leave a link
down below in case you want to try out
Zenrop. Believe me, this is probably one
of the best solutions anyone who's just
starting out with e-commerce should try.
All right, so now, let me walk you guys
through on how I'm going to turn all of
my still images into animated clips that
look just like this. So, we're going to
head back over to my GPT that we use to
create all of our image prompts. And at
the very end of the process, it's going
to ask you to upload your generated
images in order so that it can help you
to create video prompts, which is going
to animate every single one of those
images. And then I just uploaded my
first five images based on the first
five prompts that it created for me. And
from there, it was able to create all of
my video prompts to animate all of those
images. However, I did make a slight
tweak where I just asked them to add
some directions of sound effects in the
prompts, too. This way we also get the
animated visual but also the sound
effect which is really great for our
hook. So now you're probably wondering
what is the platform that I'm using to
generate all these animated visuals that
you're seeing here. Well, this platform
is called Clean AI which I think has one
of the best models out there that
creates really realistic looking
visuals. I'll leave a link down below so
that you can sign up and get some free
credits to generate your first few
videos. Once you're inside the platform,
you want to go on the lefth hand side
and click on video. Then go to the image
to video tab and on this drop down here
you can select whatever model is
available and I personally recommend
going with cleaning 2.1 as it's really
cheap in credits and it can usually get
the results that you're looking for.
However, if you're working with really
complex scenes and your prompts are
super long and really descriptive, then
clean 2.1 master can do a better job of
understanding those prompts and get you
the results that you want. However, like
I said, nine times out of 10 you're
probably going to get the results that
you need just by using the normal clean
2.1 model. So after selecting your
model, you just want to upload the image
that you want to animate. In this case,
I'm going to upload this image that I
created from Sora, which we're going to
use as the base image to make it
explode. And then if we scroll down
here, you're going to notice that
there's a box to input our prompt. So
this is where my GPT comes in, where we
have all of our video prompts, and I can
simply copy the very first prompt that
it created for me. Then just paste it
into the prompt box. And this is
optional. You can choose whether you
want a 5 or 10second clip. So if we go
with 5 seconds, it's going to cost us 35
credits. But if we go with the 10-second
option, it's pretty much just going to
cost double. And I would say nine times
out of 10, you can get most of the
footage that you need just by using
5-second video clips. And then over
here, you can choose whether you want
one or four different outputs. I would
recommend sticking to one output. This
way, you can really see the results that
you get. And then slowly make changes to
your prompt if you're not getting the
results that you want. This way, you can
avoid burning too many credits. And
lastly, as we scroll down further,
you're going to notice that there is an
option for sound effects, which is
currently free for now. And I'm going to
leave this checked on because I want
that sound effect. And this is exactly
what I have in my prompt to make that
come to life. And then once everything
is good to go, you're going to click on
generate. And then you just wait a few
minutes. And this is exactly how I was
able to get this result here of that
bottle exploding, which I then used as
the hook of my full video ad, as you
guys saw. So once you've created your
first animated scene, it's pretty much a
rinse and repeat process from here.
You're going to go back into the GPT.
You're going to copy the prompt for your
second image. You're going to go back
into cling, upload that second image.
You're going to paste that prompt into
the box. You're going to generate the
video, wait a few minutes, and then
you're going to end up with your second
animated scene just like this. And
again, you're going to keep doing this
until you have enough scenes that you
can work with so that you can match it
up to the script for your video. And
that is exactly what I did here. And
with that being said, let me show you
the full results of the video I created.
>> This new blender is so powerful, it just
might explode. Meet the Jet Smooth
portable blender. It crushes frozen
fruit, ice, and nuts in seconds without
any cords. Just toss in your
ingredients, hit the button, and it
blends everything smooth right in the
bottle. And cleaning literally takes 10
seconds. It's rechargeable, compact, and
goes anywhere. Grab yours now for just
$49 with free shipping. Don't wait.
These always sell out fast. Tap the link
to get yours before they're gone.
>> So, a few things that I want to mention
about this video. Firstly, I know it's
not 100% perfect. There may be a few
scenes if you look close enough where
the portable blender doesn't look the
same as some of the scenes before it.
But of course, this is just a current
flaw with AI, but I think for the most
part it did a really good job of keeping
most of the scenes pretty consistent.
Secondly, the very last scene that you
guys saw with the portable blender in
its branded packaging was really just a
concept photo that I created straight
out of Chat GPT. Of course, if you're
going to include this into your own
video ad, you want to make sure that the
package actually looks like the same
package that is being delivered to your
customers. And lastly, I wanted to
mention that while the process I showed
you guys to create this video seems
really simple, do keep in mind that it
does take a lot of trial and error in
order to get all of the scenes and the
visuals that you want out of cling. And
like I said earlier in this video, the
GPTs that I've created is not 100%
perfect. And all of the video prompts
and even the image prompts are not
always going to give you the results
that you want. And sometimes if you
really want to get the results that
you're looking for, it does require a
little bit of your own intuition and a
little bit of your own prompting skills.
For example, I created this image by
using a prompt that I wrote completely
by myself. And then I uploaded that
image to cling to create this little
animation, which I also wrote out by
myself as well. And this ended up being
the scene that I put in my final video
ad instead of the one that the GPT
recommended for me. And again, this was
just simply by using my own creativity
here. And just one last final tip for my
GPT, you don't have to go through the
full process of creating image prompts
and video prompts all in order. And
instead what you can do is that you
could take an image that you generated
by yourself and then you can just upload
it into the GPT and then just ask it to
help you create a video prompt just
based on that image. And you can see
that it's able to create a full video
prompt based on that image. And this is
something that you can also potentially
test if you want to try to animate that
with Cling. So that's my entire process
on creating full e-commerce video ads
from scratch using AI. And if you've
made it this far into this video, I'm
also going to show you another video ad
that I've created just for fun of a
fictional character from the 1700s
discovering this portable blender for
the first time. Behold this curious
vessel which turns simple fruit into a
drink most smooth. A fine pour thick and
ready. A gentleman must always prepare
his potions properly. Such vigorous
swirling reminds me of Lady Beatatric on
the dance floor.
A fine sip so good it might lead a man
to mischief in the name of liberty. I do
proclaim this vessel a rightful tool for
all who cherish freedom and fine
refreshment.
>> So, I know that video was not perfect by
any means and the character in the video
clearly looks fake, but to be honest, I
do think videos like this could be the
future for e-commerce where you don't
technically need real people to be
advertising your products. And if you
can create some sort of fictional
character to add some humor behind the
products that you're selling, that
actually could be enough to convert
people. But, I don't know. That's just
my guess and I just wanted to show you
guys this just so you guys can see the
power of what you can actually create
with AI. And in case you do want to know
how I create fictional characters that
actually talk with my product, then let
me know down in the comments below and
I'll be more than happy to make a video
about that. But aside from that, I hope
you guys did enjoy this video. If you
did, be sure to drop a like and
subscribe to this channel and make sure
to join my free Discord group so that
you could be connected with other
like-minded entrepreneurs who are also
doing e-commerce and drop shipping. and
follow me on Twitter as I drop some tips
and strategies from time to time on what
I'm actually doing on my stores right
now. And last but not least, I want to
end this video off with a disclaimer in
that every single video ad that I showed
you guys was just for educational and
demonstration purposes only. If you do
decide to create video ads for your
products with AI, you need to make sure
that all of your content actually looks
identical to the product that you're
selling because if it's not, then you're
just going to be misleading all of your
customers and I am not responsible for
that. So again, just make sure to use AI
responsibly and use it as a supplement
for the growth and the scale of your
current stores. And with that being
said, I thank you guys so much for
watching and I'll catch you on the next
one.
[Music]